we are sailing again to break the siege and this time we're sailing with dozens of boats and with
coordinated mobilizations from 44 countries around the world this will be the biggest international
solidarity effort ever since israel implemented its horrific siege 18 years ago the genocide
against palestinians in ghaza has been escalating for 22 months israel has dropped the equivalent
of eight atomic bombs on men women and children hospitals shelters schools and homes completely
destroyed tens of thousands of unidentified victims and possibly hundreds of thousands more
unidentified victims from the bombings shootings and starvation never in history have so many
journalists un workers and health workers been killed and we simply cannot stand by while this
continues that's why the free people of the world are standing up and sailing forward and we are
calling upon you to join this initiative the global smooth flotilla a unified effort from coalitions
organizations and everyday people from across the world who have shown unwavering solidarity with the
people of palestine you have seen us trying to break the siege by sea by land and by air and you've
seen us trying to break the media blockade and break big tech's algorithms on social media and expose
complicity everywhere silence is not an option the people of gaza need us to raise our collective voices
to be in solidarity even when governments and institutions fail this is the greatest historical
call of our generation and the people of the world will not fail to answer this call on august 31st we are
sailing from spain with dozens of boats and dozens more will join on september 4th from tunisia and
other countries sailing together to break the illegal siege of gaza demand an end to the genocide and to
finally open up a humanitarian corridor and while we are at sea we're calling on everyone to support
this global movement to join the encampments and demonstration that will happen simultaneously now is the
moment to maximize pressure so we need you follow the global samud flotilla page share engage donate
but most of all register to participate captains crew journalists people with platforms organizers
medical workers and humans of the world on land or at sea we are all together and we need you come to our
launch events mobilize in your own country spread the word that the decisive moment has come to mobilize with the
palestinian people to stop genocide and demand the free palestine and the free world join us the
global samud flotilla global soon would put in the global samud flotilla the global samud flotilla